Once again, Haruhisa Kurabayashi joins the fray in the second half.
He seems to be adjusting very well to being on the first team.
There's something in his game that you might be able to incorporate into your own.
Whoa! He got the best crew!
There it is! This has to be what he meant!
Hmm? Hey, Aoi! You're not supposed to run in the hallway!
Coach Nozomi! Hey! Kurabayashi's game footage! I need everything!
Hey, what do you think you're doing? Pay attention, Aoi!
Quit spacing out, dude. Wake up!
What's your deal? You've been like a distracted zombie lately.
Uh, sorry.
You weren't even looking at the one who had the ball. Did you forget how to play?
Course not.
Seems like he's completely lost his motivation out there. What's going on?
Haven't you noticed how unfocused and lazy he's been playing all week?
You want to watch Kuribayashi play? Forget the killer pass. You should be watching footage of defenders instead.
There's something I need to confirm first.
It doesn't seem like a big deal, so I never thought about it.
Even I was taught to do it when I was a kid. How special could it be?
But I see it now. Kuribayashi goes to the extreme, doing it constantly all game long. It's a little freaky.
Anyway, I would like to watch his past games. I want to see how long he's done it, and what for.
Okay. Does this mean you're finally ready to play as a defender?
I can't say I'm ready yet, but I'm gonna do it for them.
I don't want to cause any trouble for my teammates. I need to play at a strong enough level for them.
I can't drag them down. No more!
Owie!
You were late with the shuffle again.
Hey, Owie!
Oh, jeez.
That's a lot of head turns for a single match.
Is he part chicken?
Right before he receives the ball, he turns his head left and right.
Then after he receives it, he'll do it again.
How does he not snap his damn neck?
It looks like it takes him less than a second.
He's doing it when the ball isn't near him.
It's all totally automatic.
Turning my head like that would be a good skill.
I'd know which players were around, and how many,
which would tell me what needs to be done.
Then I could plan my next move.
These are different from the ones I learned when I was little.
It won't be a simple adjustment.
I'll have to learn his method from scratch.
Idiot!
In soccer, turning one's head is the most basic of the basics,
but only a few can make full use of the technique.
The rest just go through the motions without any strategic intention.
A player should do it right before receiving the ball.
Looking all around gives him a grasp on the state of the field in that moment.
Also, it demonstrates to the other team that he is aware of his surroundings,
discouraging them from tackling him,
and making his teammates feel comfortable linking up.
Listen to me.
By watching Kuribayashi's game,
you could find something to incorporate into your own.
Good job, Ali.
This is exactly what I was referring to.
Just keep it up.
This isn't working for me!
I keep turning my head in all sorts of directions,
and I don't know what I'm looking for!
Screw being a fullback!
I feel like I'm causing even more problems for my team now!
Whoa!
That's scary!
Wait, wait, wait!
Huh?
I'm over this chicken dance for today.
It's a lot easier said than done.
Ashito!
Down the wing!
Crap!
I wasn't looking in front of me!
Stay calm!
I can just pass to Togashien!
Huh?
Right.
Tell everyone to come in, Benson.
I'm ready to announce the starters for the third match.
Man, it's been a while.
I wonder if everyone in the cafeteria missed me.
Oh, there she is!
Hi, Hana!
This nice young man has been waiting to speak to you!
I'm sure it's frustrating.
Hey.
Hi.
So I know these last games were rough,
but after giving so much to the B team as a forward,
it truly must be a gut punch not to even make the bench now.
Oh, well.
I've never played fullback.
I can't just transform overnight.
You don't seem as frustrated as I thought you'd be.
I wanted to ask you.
Before, when you told me to watch Kurabayashi's gameplay,
was it about the head turns he does?
Yes.
Do you know of any drills to help learn that technique?
Like, how do I master?
I mean, it's a lot to be aware of.
I want to be able to do it unconsciously.
Like him.
This is it!
This is a test!
I want to be a manager!
This is my chance to show off what I can do!
So you...
you made this meal plan?
Dang.
I had a feeling I was missing a page on this one.
It's quite impressive.
The lunch lady told me you were the one who laid it out.
She worked really hard on it
and even consulted our menu for healthy options.
All for a player she liked.
Well, that's so sweet!
I didn't expect something like this out of Manager Fukuda's sister.
You would come by to help all the time
when we were on the junior youth team together.
Wow! So cool!
The great Kurabayashi, a world-renowned player, knows who I am!
You used to patch me up when I was injured.
So yeah.
Whoa!
I thought that might be you, Kurabayashi!
Asperion's shining star and our great hope!
Um, thank you.
We'll be counting on you in the next game!
Love you!
Later!
Everybody loves you!
Guess that happens when you're world famous-
I want to be the best.
In the whole world.
Do you think you could help me?
There.
I need a meal plan just like that.
For real.
But I'm a picky eater.
I refuse to eat peppers.
Or carrots.
What? Are you a child?
Still, you're joking, right?
I mean, it's not like high-end or anything.
You put so much work into it.
I'm assuming that's what you want to do for a career.
Sports nutrition, I mean.
I play in a professional league, you know.
I would be a walking billboard for new clients.
Just think about it.
Okay, fine.
On one condition.
What's that?
Well, um, my friend Ashita wants to play like you someday.
Could you maybe give him some point-
Uh-huh.
What?
Nothing.
I'll get started on it.
Hmm?
You have to find a way to make turning your head a habit, Aoi.
Consciously incorporate it into your daily training.
Hmm?
Huh?
Start with ball juggling.
Oh.
Then, do a kick, and while it's high in the air,
look left and right, and catch it.
Also, don't just turn your head.
Try to spot something and make a note of it as you look each way.
For example, a pebble, a leaf.
I catch it on my foot, and then I repeat it.
Huh?
I-
Um, it's pretty basic.
Sure, you already know.
Your ball control's awesome.
Wow, you really think so?
Yeah, and you're right.
I do know that drill.
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
But, I never knew I was supposed to spot things.
That makes sense.
I'll do it.
At least a thousand times.
I'll have it down by the next match.
He's being so positive about it.
They made him change his position,
and then didn't even put him on the bench for the game.
But instead of sulking,
he's taking the time to work on his skills.
It hasn't even been a week
since I saw his face looking so lost.
He's so cute.
That pass I made to Otomo earlier.
I did it unconsciously.
I have no idea how I did that.
The only thing I changed was turning my head.
I wasn't looking at anything specific,
but something happened.
For a split second.
What exactly was that?
I feel like it's happened before.
It was super quick, but I remember it.
I saw it very clearly.
Up until then, it was in the corner of my mind.
It resembled a bunch of ants swarming around.
Suddenly, I was able to connect to that vision.
I don't think there are words to truly describe it.
But who cares?
It happened.
I turned my head, and something changed.
So I'll stay out and practice
until I'm just as good as Kurabayashi.
I might be about to grasp onto something great.
For real.
Your vision's really wide.
Vision.
The situation's critical.
We've lost four games in a row.
You see this?
This is our team.
Right there in the relegation zone.
Even the second tier team plays
at Tokyo Metropolis League level.
That's the strength of Asperion youth.
And if we are relegated,
it limits our team's potential next year
and for years after.
I agree with you.
We have worked too hard to lose it all now.
Not getting demoted is the least I expect of B team.
I may have moved up to A team,
but I'm still pulling for everyone on B team to succeed.
I know what you're capable of.
I'm sorry, you guys.
It's not just Tachibana.
The forwards in general aren't scoring enough.
The defenders aren't doing so hot either.
We've let way too many goals get through lately.
Ask Togashi.
He's so committed to ignoring me
that he won't even make eye contact.
And we're both defenders.
I've let you down.
I'm sorry.
I haven't scored any goals at all.
There's plenty of blame to go around, Tachibana,
so don't take it all on yourself.
Gotta ease up, man.
Hey, be real.
What's with Coach?
Do you think he's bringing Aoi back as a forward?
Oh, that reminds me.
Ashito isn't here yet, is he?
Is he running late?
I really hope he wouldn't miss such an important meeting.
You know what I mean?
Aoi stayed back as usual.
He wanted to keep practicing.
You haven't noticed?
He trains for an hour or so after we get out.
He's done it every day for the past month, at least.
We don't have time to talk about players
who aren't even on the bench.
We gotta focus on the actual team.
Offense, let's focus.
We're out of time.
Cause soon, we play the top team on this board.
It's time to step it up.
That can't be.
Are these stats real?
Six wins, zero losses, and a goal difference of 17?
Were they always this strong?
I don't know anything for sure,
but I heard they got a new manager this year.
One of their high-ranking junior youth coaches got promoted.
So, yeah.
Regardless, their strength's extraordinary.
They're the last team we want to face,
especially in the state we're in right now.
Wait a sec, Tachibana.
Didn't you used to play for Musashino?
You're still out here practicing this late?
Hey there, Tachibana.
Aw, crap!
Did I miss the team meeting?
I'm so sorry.
I figured since I'm not even on the bench,
I didn't have much to contribute anyway.
So I decided to prioritize practicing.
I'll just be a little longer.
You can head back to the dorm without me.
You know, I think you're amazing.
I am?
You don't sulk.
Like ever.
I don't know anyone who works harder than you.
Is that so?
It is.
Even when you're not on the field,
you pay close attention to every game
and cheer us all on.
Okay, stop.
I was with you up until the cheering part,
but I am working on ways to help.
Huh?
All that stuff's new, by the way.
Really?
I used to be the king of Solking.
I would refuse to watch any game I didn't play in.
I mean, that's super frustrating, you know?
But this past month,
I really started to think seriously about my vision.
And I'm actually learning a lot
just by sitting on the sidelines.
Tons!
I watch and think about what I would do in that position.
Like, I'll notice how a guy didn't look toward the middle
and ask what would have happened if he did.
I work out scenarios like little puzzles
as I observe the game.
It makes the time fly by.
So I'm not the perfect cheerleader.
Sorry.
Can you teach me how to be just like you?
Hmm?
Hmm.
Hey!
Tachibana!
Ashito!
We need to eat our feelings!
You want to join?
How about Okonomiyaki?
Yeah, sounds good!
You're in, right, Tachibana?
So, which place are we going to?
Let's see.
It is close.
Mustachino's number one.
The game against Asperion youth is coming up.
I can't wait to see Tachibana and Otomo and Aoi.
I wonder how much they've improved.
What do you mean you don't want to go to Musashino?
Isn't that your hometown, Tachibana?
What's your damage, bro?
It is my hometown.
That's why I don't want to go.
Please don't do this to me, Tachibana!
My mind's in a full-blown Okonomiyaki mode right now
and I can't eat anywhere else!
Until I start contributing to Asperion,
I'd rather not return home at disappointment.
I don't believe any of that, Bull.
You're always going home whenever we have some time off.
Really?
I visit my grandfather in Sugamo.
He lives alone, so I check up on him.
Aw, you angel.
Anyway, I'm keeping that promise to myself.
You know, I feel you on not wanting to go home
until you can show him you've accomplished something.
But we're just going to eat.
Enough talking!
You know, Tachibana, you can be a little dramatic at times.
Just saying.
Stop taking matches so personal.
Like when we're losing pretty big, you get all depressed, bro.
It's just a game.
It's not that huge a deal.
Because our team hasn't been scoring.
And as a forward, that makes me feel responsible.
You lost me!
I don't give two craps long as I'm playing well.
Because I know if we lose, it's not my fault.
It's someone else's.
Now, if we win, that's 100% my fault.
It's that easy.
I get super nervous right before a match.
Once it's over, though, that's it for me.
It's in the past, and that's where it stays.
Gotta move on.
How about you?
I don't know.
I don't really play much these days.
It doesn't matter.
Honestly, I get how you feel, Tachibana.
This is the way I see it.
Anytime I play in a game, I'm responsible for the moves I make.
Let me put it a different way.
It's my fault if we win or lose.
And that makes me the most powerful player on the team.
What are you saying?
So, like, when we lose,
I start thinking about how to help the team win the next game.
I get so excited for the next match
that I start practicing for it right then.
You are the wind beneath our wings, Ashito.
Let me see.
You're supposed to be right by the train station.
Tachibana!
You want to help since this is your town?
Oh, my gosh!
No way!
It's Nakano!
Is that Aoi?
And Tachibana?
And Ultimo?
Nakano!
I can't believe it!
It's been forever!
I knew it!
One glance and I just knew it!
Are we going to eat or not?
Who's this guy?
It's Nakano!
He was our brother in arms back during the Asperion tryouts!
Anyway, how you been, man?
So he's one of the losers that didn't make it.
They consider him a brother in arms.
Seriously!
But that's it!
His round eyes haven't changed one bit!
They're very cute.
Hey, Nakano.
That kid.
I don't understand.
Oh, yeah.
About that.
I played for Tokyo Musashino's youth team.
Huh?
Tachibana's old team?
What the heck do you mean?
After failing in the tryouts, I was scouted.
Manager Satake recruited me.
That's who's coaching us now.
Obviously, we both accepted.
We would have been crazy not to.
You both?
Nakano.
Huh?
What?
Kaneda?
No way!
You've got to be kidding me!
You're playing on the same team as Nakano now?
That's amazing!
We can all go to dinner and catch up.
Whoa, look at you.
You've blown up at least one size.
Huh?
Get your hands off me!
It makes no sense.
I never expected you to get past the first round.
During those stupid tryouts.
I couldn't focus because of you guys.
You ruined it.
And for that, I will never forgive you!
チャー chains are nailed.
Why does stupid tryouts?
I don't care what happens.
You're not right.
I do not know.
I will never forgive you.
I will never forgive you, man.
сбasaki out.
I will never be right away.
You're late.
I will never forget you.
zwischen you once said...
Excuse me, kau Anti-
ency, you're welcome.
You're right.
Not ma'aları, I will never forget you.
Next time on Awashi, Tokyo Metropolis League Match 7, Tama Sports University High School.